<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Southern Southern California's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Andy Cleaves, a top Real Estate Agent in Southern California, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. Her Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 13:08:29 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 13:08:29 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Top Producer Eileen Rivera Turns Hard Work into Major Success</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/clgxJfqqVRk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our most recent agent interview, top producer Eileen Rivera joined us to share her tips and tricks for succeeding in real estate. Given that she closed $68 million in volume on 85 transactions last year, she’s definitely more than qualified to offer this advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The information Eileen shared during our interview was so incredible that we’re going to share it with you today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the interview. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;00:23 — An introduction to today’s interview&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;00:55 — What our Eileen’s top lead sources?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;01:33 — Eileen explains how she works her geo farm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;03:27 — Eileen shares the size of her farm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;04:36 — How does Eileen handle online leads?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;06:05 — How Eileen handles open houses&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:44 — What kind of mindset should an agent have to succeed, and how should they protect that mindset?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:08 — What got Eileen to where she is today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15:05 — Eileen shares her goals for 2019&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18:05 — Eileen explains the value of work ethic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18:44 — A few closing words for today’s interview&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-top-producer-eileen-rivera-turns-hard-work-into-major-success.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-top-producer-eileen-rivera-turns-hard-work-into-major-success.html</guid>
        
        <category>Top Producers</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Interview with Real Estate Superstar Dave Robles</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/XpFb4jLxMSM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, we were fortunate enough to sit down and speak with Dave Robles—a rockstar agent who had $48 million in closed sales volume in 2018.  The insight Dave offered into his success was so amazing that we’ve decided to bring you the full interview, today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the interview. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;00:25 — How Dave finds his leads&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;01:02 — How big is Dave’s farm, and how does he reach the people within it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;04:05 — How Dave works his database&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;07:25 — What is the best way for newer agents to grow their business?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;09:21 — Dave explains the size and breakdown of his team&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:01 — What content does Dave and his team share in their emails?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;14:33 — Dave shares his goals for 2019&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;16:14 — Dave’s top tip for new agents&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;17:25 — A few closing words&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/an-interview-with-real-estate-superstar-dave-robles.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/an-interview-with-real-estate-superstar-dave-robles.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Elite Agent Success Story: Bryan Van Zee</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mbalG3628VU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve got an amazing story to share with you today. Meet Bryan Van Zee: Bryan is a new agent who closed 15 transactions in his first year and is well on his way to close even more soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the video. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:35 - Bryan talks about his first three months in the real estate business&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:15 - Bryan explains the “breakthrough” moment that changed everything for him&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5:09 - Bryan shares the tools and resources he uses to succeed in real estate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:07 - How Bryan became the top agent in his firm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9:21 - Bryan explains his routine for hosting open houses&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10:47 - Bryan shares his top tips for new agents&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;14:00 - A few parting words about working in real estate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;14:54 - How you can reach out to us and get started on a success story of your own&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions for us in the meantime, don’t hesitate to reach out and give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 16:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/an-elite-agent-success-story-bryan-van-zee.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/an-elite-agent-success-story-bryan-van-zee.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
